Every parent wants
the answer to one question.
Is my child on track?
We built an AI tutor that knows
the South African syllabus.
NSC. IEB. Cambridge.
Cites the textbook.
Past papers are marked
the way an examiner would.
Not generic.
Markscheme-aware.
And on Family Pro, parents see
mastery forecasts per child.
Bursary deadlines.
Celebration alerts.
Real-time feedback on SBA drafts
against the rubric.
Not a writing tip generator.
A coach.
Tutors get AI lesson plans
and auto parent reports.
The unfair advantage
for SA tutors.
When the load gets heavy,
the app knows.
Stress trends. A real counsellor.
Aptiverse.
A calmer matric. Genuinely.
Built in South Africa,
for South Africa.
We built this because we wished
we'd had it ourselves.
Book a demo at aptiverse.co.za.
aptiverse.co.za